{
    "id": "1a4706deb1674e1e98cd547f8210cc86",
    "title": "Past simple and past perfect tense exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9664eaa0b285430a881a42d0eb94efee",
            "title": "Past Simple And Past Perfect Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "By the time the fire fighters ……………., the fire ……………… many huts.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "arrived, destroyed",
                        "had arrived, destroyed",
                        "arrived, had destroyed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was not …………….. to write the exam, because he ……………….. his hall ticket.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "permitted, did not bring",
                        "permitted, had not brought",
                        "permitted, has not brought"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Long before the chief guest ………………., the invitees  …………….. .",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "had arrived, had assembled",
                        "arrived, assembled",
                        "arrived, had assembled"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you …………….. your application in time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sent",
                        "have sent",
                        "had sent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The police …………… the thief. They ……………. for him for two months.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "caught, looked",
                        "had caught, had been looking",
                        "caught, had been looking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If they ………………. the Principal, he would have helped them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "met",
                        "have met",
                        "had met"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. to him, as I ………………… to him formally.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have not spoken, was not introduced",
                        "did not speak, was not introduced",
                        "had not spoken, was not introduced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "By the time we ………….. the station, the train  …………… .",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "had reached, had left",
                        "reached, left",
                        "reached, had left"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If Balu ………….. the secretary earlier, he …………… him a job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see, would give",
                        "saw, would have given",
                        "had seen, would have given"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If Raju ……………. in our team, we ……………. .",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "were, would win",
                        "were, would have won",
                        "were, will win"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}